Guide to the Helen E. Hokinson Cartoons for The New Yorker
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Portfolio 6, Series VI
  - 57. [Two matrons seated in rocking chairs conversing on porch of house at the seashore.], 1936 (Box 13, Folder 301)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 15 x 20". AA3814 written in blue crayon on verso. Kraft paper cover sheet date stamped AUG 1 1936.
  - 58. [Three matrons (two conversing) near elevator in foyer of an apartment house.], 1945 (Box 13, Folder 302)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 14 x 23". Correction overlay on left half of drawing. A8615 written in blue crayon on verso. Kraft paper cover sheet dated in pencil 6-16-45.
  - 59. "You know perfectly well you've got to lose three pounds if you intend to go to Madison Square Garden!" (Box 13, Folder 303)
    Pencil, 15 x 20", rough sketch, unsigned. Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing over previously erased caption partially visible.
  - 60. "I don't really like cocktails, I just think I do/I just like to mix things up for my friends." (Box 13, Folder 304)
    Pencil, 15 3/4 x 22 1/8", rough sketch, unsigned. Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing over previously erased caption partially visible.
  - 61. "—and next week we are going sailing out together into the new era." (Box 14, Folder 305)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 15 x 22". Caption written in pencil on right margin near foot of drawing. A9209 written in blue crayon on verso.
  - 62. [Two matrons conversing on sidewalk across from a large church.] (Box 14, Folder 306)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 14 x 23 1/8". Correction onlay over right half of drawing. AC1487 written in blue crayon on verso.
  - 63. "Do you all give up?", 1935 (Box 14, Folder 307)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 20 x 15". Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing, and on Kraft paper cover sheet with date stamp SEPT 14 1935. AA3594 written in blue crayon on verso.
  - 64. So You're Going to Have Your Picture Taken! (Box 14, Folder 308)
    A sequence of 12 panel drawings. Black ink and gray wash over pencil, each drawing 4 x 5" on two sheets, six per sheet, each 22 1/8 x 15 1/8". Correction overlay covers all of drawing #7. Title written in black ink at head across both sheets. Captions written in black ink at foot of each drawing. A4930 written in pencil on verso of both sheets.
  - 65. "I wouldn't do this for anybody but Richard Hudnut." (Box 14, Folder 309)
  - 66. The Country Dog Show. (Box 14, Folder 310)
    Four vignettes, black ink and gray wash over pencil, the drawings, various sizes, on a single sheet, 19 x 16". Title at head and caption at foot of fourth drawing—Franklin gets a big kiss—written in pencil.
  - 67. "How much are you asking for Maurice Evans?" or "How much is Maurice Evans?" (Box 14, Folder 311)
    Pencil, 14 x 22 1/8", rough sketch, unsigned. Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing, and typed on a slip attached to drawing.
  - 68. [Scene at rehearsal of an amateur theatrical company—matron director conversing with cast.], 1938 (Box 14, Folder 312)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 15 7/8 x 22 3/4". AA7739 written in blue crayon on verso. Kraft paper cover sheet date stamped SEP 17 1938.
  - 69. [Scene at rehearsal of amateur theatrical company—matron director directing three members of the cast.], 1938 (Box 14, Folder 313)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 15 x 22 5/8". AA7386 written in blue crayon on verso. Kraft paper cover sheet date stamped APR 16 1938.
  - 70. [Scene at rehearsal of amateur theatrical company—matron director conversing with two members of the cast.] (Box 14, Folder 314)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 14 x 23". Erased caption partially visible at foot of drawing. A2806 written in blue crayon on verso.
  - 71. "This is doing me so much good. I'm going back to Boston a new person." (Box 14, Folder 315)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 14 x 22". Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing and cancelled. A6824 written in blue crayon on verso.
  - 72. [Scene at rehearsal of amateur theatrical company—cast at table reading on stage.], 1941 (Box 14, Folder 316)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 14 x 23". Erased caption partially visible at. foot of drawing. A2833 written in blue crayon on verso. Kraft paper cover sheet date stamped NOV 1 1941.
  - 73. [Two matrons having iced tea on porch watch approach of a UPS driver.], 1941 (Box 14, Folder 317)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 14 x 22". Erased caption partially visible at foot of drawing. A2584 written in blue crayon on verso. Kraft paper cover sheet date stamped JUN 28 1941.
  - 74. So You're Going to Bermuda & Ride a Bicycle! (Box 14, Folder 318)
    A sequence of twelve panel drawings. Black ink and pencil, each drawing approximately 4 x 4 " on a sheet 17 x 22", unsigned. Title written in black ink at head of drawings; captions written in pencil at foot of each drawing.
  - 75. "Bertha! Stop flirting!" (Box 14, Folder 319)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 15 3/4 x 22 3/4". Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing over previously erased partially visible caption.
  - 76. "Oh Mr. Speer, you neglected my Dante.", 1933 (Box 14, Folder 320)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 14 x 22 1/8". Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing. A9885 written in blue crayon and date 4/15/33 in pencil on verso.
  - 77. "Yes lady, I'll be careful.", 1930 (Box 14, Folder 321)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 14 1/8 x 22". Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing, and cancelled. A7080 written in blue crayon and date 8/2/30 in pencil on verso.
  - 78. [Matron and daughter in stand at a sporting event.]; cartoon by Perry Barlow, 1931 (Box 14, Folder 322)
    Black crayon, charcoal and gray wash over pencil, 17 x 19 5/8", signed P Barlow. Two tears at head, three at foot, one in right margin, 1/2-2" in length. Verso contains rough pencil sketch of a young woman in hat and coat, waving. A8660 written in red crayon and date 11/14/31 in pencil on verso.
  - 79. "But if we disband our Defend America Committee, won't Russia take it as a sign of yielding?" (Box 14, Folder 323)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 15 x 19". Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing. AC 3594 written in blue pencil on verso.
  - 80. "May I date Betty up for the movies? We've known each other two years." (Box 4, Folder 55)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 17 7/8 x 13 1/8". Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing. A5422 written in blue crayon on verso.
  - 81. "You must go to my beauty doctor. She'd make another person of you." (Box 4, Folder 56)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 12 x 10". Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing. A4173 written in black crayon on verso.
  - 82. "I don't play kid stuff at all." (Box 4, Folder 57)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 13 x 16 7/8". Caption written in pencil in bottom lower left corner of drawing, alternate caption in pencil at foot, and notation—Morris Baum Theatrical enterprises—in pencil at head of drawing. A2758 written in pencil on verso.
  - 83. "Why Don't You Com...... Yes, Why Don't I?" (Box 14, Folder 324)
    A sequence of eight panel drawings about the disappointments of traveling for a weekend visit. Black ink and gray wash over pencil, the drawings each approximately 5 x 5" on a sheet 13 x 20 1/8". Title (partially missing) written in black ink on overlays at head over previously erased title and at foot, and captions in black ink at foot of each drawing.
- Portfolio 7, Series VII
  - 1. "She never graduated with us—it's just that she told her husband she did." (Box 15, Folder 325)
    Pencil, 20 x 15", rough sketch, unsigned. Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing. Alternate captions: a) "She may have been a nitwit, but that never stopped Princeton."; b) "I'm just looking to see if he says anything about New Canaan." typed on slips attached to drawing. 2 x 3" piece missing from upper left corner.
  - 2. [Sailor and girl seated on park bench.], 1930 (Box 10, Folder 174)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 7 x 5 7/8". A5508 written in blue crayon and date 5/10/30 in pencil on verso.
  - 3. "No ma'am, we didn't take the position. They wanted us to fold and we insert." (Box 4, Folder 58)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 14 3/8 x 15 5/8", unsigned. Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing. 4710 written in pencil on verso.
  - 4. "But if a girl goes to Briarcliff and to Arthur Murray's do you think she really needs Smith?" (Box 15, Folder 326)
    Pencil, 14 1/4 x 18 3/4", rough sketch. unsigned. Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing over previously erased partially visible caption.
  - 5."I'm so thrilled! Milton's going to treat me to have my walls glazed." (Box 4, Folder 59)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 10 1/2 x 10 1/2". Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing. Lower portion of mat torn away with remains of caption (repetition of the above?) visible. A48 (last digits of number missing) written in pencil on verso.
  - 6. "Sit down, Oiving, you don't want one of these ladies to get your seat, do you?", 1931 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 12 x 10". Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing and cancelled. 489 (letter and first digit missing) and date 4/25/31 written in pencil on verso.
  - 7. [Man and woman dancing.] (Box 10, Folder 175)
    Black ink over gray pencil, 4 x 2 7/8", rough sketch, unsigned.
  - 8. "A-avez-vous Ulysses?", 1930 (Box 15, Folder 327)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 20 x 15". Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing and cancelled. Notation: (a friend of mine gave me this idea, she said she submitted a drawing of it to the N. Yorker but it was rejected. I think it's an awfully funny idea.) written in pencil in lower right corner margin and cancelled. AS905 written in blue crayon and date May 24, 1930 in pencil on verso.
  - 9. [Woman in robe holding small loaf of French bread to her mouth.] (Box 10, Folder 176)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 2 x 4", rough sketch, unsigned. Lower left corner missing. Sketch further developed in panel cartoon "Petit Dejeuner" (Series VII, drawing 81).
  - 10. "Where are the guns, please?" (Box 10, Folder 177)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 10 x 8 1/2", rough sketch, unsigned. Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing, and cancelled.
  - 11. [Scene at country dog show.] (Box 15, Folder 328)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 14 x 19 3/8", rough sketch, unsigned. Verso contains notation—Only, if needed—written in pencil.
  - 12. [Young woman in fur coat confronting saleslady at dress pattern counter.] (Box 10, Folder 178)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 10 x 7 1/8", rough sketch, unsigned. 8 x 3/4" strip cut away from left margin, 2 x l" piece missing from right margin, 1/2 x 1 3/4" piece missing from lower right corner.
  - 13. "Mother's only going to the dentist—you'd be bored to death." (Box 4, Folder 61)
    Pencil, 14 7/8 x 16 7/8", rough sketch, unsigned. Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing over previously erased caption, and typed on a slip attached to drawing.
  - 14. "Will you please whistle for a taxi with a radio?" (Box 4, Folder 62)
    Gray wash and pencil, 12 1/4 x 18 5/8", rough sketch, unsigned. Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing.
  - 15. [Three matrons playing croquet.] (Box 4, Folder 63)
    Black ink and watercolor, 13 3/4 x 11 1/8", unsigned. Rough sketch for cover.
  - 16. "I would ask for a full tank if both dogs weren't on their way to get married." (Box 4, Folder 64)
    Pencil on tissue mounted on paper, 11 x 16 3/4", rough sketch, unsigned. Caption written in pencil on matt below drawing, notation—(always liked this situation)—written in pencil on mat in upper right corner. Upper right corner of drawing missing.
  - 17. [Matron presenting bouquet to her butcher.], 1946 (Box 15, Folder 329)
    Progressive proof of cover for June 22, 1946, issue with color bars, 21 7/8 x 13 1/4".
  - 18. [Two matrons with spouses trailing, dressed for tennis, proceeding across club lawn.] (Box 4, Folder 65)
    Watercolor over pencil, 16 7/8 x 13 7/8", unsigned. Notation—left Mrs. Grisner—written in pencil in right margin. Rough sketch for cover. See Series VII, drawing 104 for an expanded cartoon version.
  - 19. [Matron with Scottie and saleslady trying on dog blankets.] (Box 4, Folder 66)
    Watercolor over pencil, 17 3/4 x 11 7/8", unsigned. Rough sketch for cover.
  - 20. "Be sure and let me know the minute somebody makes a clock." (Box 15, Folder 330)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 15 x 12 1/4", rough sketch, unsigned. Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing. Title: THE GIRLS By Helen E. Hokinson (her signature) written in pencil at head of drawing.
  - 21. [Disgruntled maid sitting in lounge chair on patio viewed from the house by her employers.] (Box 4, Folder 67)
    Black ink and watercolor over pencil, 12 x 8 7/8", unsigned. Notation—Newcombe's house—written in pencil on lower right corner of mount. Rough sketch for cover.
  - 22. "Quick, Nora—What's a county in Ireland that begins with D?" (Box 4, Folder 68)
    Pencil, 12 1/4 x 18", rough sketch, unsigned. Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing over previously erased partially visible caption, and typed on a slip attached to the drawing.
  - 23. "I'm awfully tired of books about things." (Box 4, Folder 69)
    Pencil, 13 3/4 x 16 7/8", rough sketch, unsigned. Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing over previously erased partially visible caption.
  - 24. "No, no, no, Mr. Stokely! You can suggest centuries of oppression better than that." (Box 4, Folder 70)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 14 x 17 3/8". Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing over previously erased partially visible caption.
  - 25. "Did you meet any nice boys this summer?" "Yes I met a swell boy scout; and what a man! Just covered with medals!" (Box 15, Folder 331)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 20 x 15". Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing, and cancelled; alternate wording in right margin. A5166 written in pencil on verso.
  - 26. Walking out on Stravinsky's "Sacre." "Mr. Damrosch will hear of this." (Box 4, Folder 71)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 6 5/8 x 6", unsigned. Caption written in pencil on mount below drawing. Notation—HOK A1736 (orig; cut missing 9/13/28) in pencil in upper right corner of mat. A1736 written in pencil on verso.
  - 27. [Woman making flower arrangement while husband looks on.] (Box 10, Folder 179)
    Pencil, 6 x 5 1/8", rough sketch, unsigned. Notation—making flower arrangement on husband's desk dark somber room—written in pencil in lower right corner. Drawn on verso of Hokinson printed invoice form.
  - 28. [Scene at buffet party.] (Box 10, Folder 180)
    Pencil, 6 x 5 1/8", rough sketch, unsigned. Rough sketch for cover. Drawn on verso of Hokinson printed invoice form.
  - 29. [Matron and child on a see-saw with nanny standing by.] (Box 4, Folder 72)
    Watercolor over pencil, 11 x 8 3/4", unsigned. Rough sketch for cover.
  - 30. [Drawing of red barn and six colored balls.] (Box 10, Folder 181)
    Watercolor over pencil, 10 7/8 x 8 3/8", rough sketch, unsigned.
  - 31. [Figure studies—five women and a man.] (Box 5, Folder 73)
    Colored crayons, 11 7/8 x 8 7/8", unsigned, sketch torn from sketch pad.
  - 32. [Parson arrives for a visit.] (Box 5, Folder 74)
    Watercolor over pencil, 10 x 7 5/8", unsigned. Rough sketch for cover.
  - 33. "Let's go have tea after the retrievers." (Box 5, Folder 75)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 15 5/8 x 18", rough sketch, unsigned. Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing above two alternate captions. Torn through center from head to foot.
  - 34. [Cowboy on horseback with Kansas pennant.] (Box 5, Folder 76)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 17 3/4 x 10 1/4", unsigned. A4871 written in black crayon on verso.
  - 35. The rough rodeo boys are in town. (Box 5, Folder 77)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 9 3/4 x 18 1/2", unsigned. Title written in pencil at foot of drawing, and cancelled. Lower left corner cut away. A4871 written in black crayon on verso, part of the A cut away.
  - 36. [Woman commenting to a man at a concert.] (Box 10, Folder 182)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 5 x 5", rough sketch, unsigned. Upper left and right corners cut away.
  - 37. [Rear view of man and woman in evening dress walking.] (Box 10, Folder 183)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 8 5/8 x 6 1/4", rough sketch, unsigned. Upper and lower right corners cut away.
  - 38. [A group of men and women in evening dress.] (Box 10, Folder 184)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 8 1/4 x 9 1/4".
  - 39. So You're Going to Sublet Your Apartment. (Box 5, Folder 78)
    A series of twelve panel drawings. Black ink and gray wash over pencil, the drawings, each approximately 4 x 6", on three sheets—four drawings per sheet, the sheets 13 x 15 7/8". Title written in pencil at foot of drawings across the three sheets, and cancelled; captions written in black ink at foot of each drawing. A3857 written in pencil on verso of each sheet.
  - 40. [Portrait of a bald man in glasses and overcoat reading a large book.] (Box 10, Folder 185)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 9 3/8 x 7 3/4", unsigned. A4370 written in black crayon on verso. Notation—held from 4370 written in black crayon on tissue cover sheet.
  - 41. [Meeting of a ladies club.] (Box 5, Folder 79)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 13- 3/4 x 17 7/8". A4383 written in blue crayon on verso.
  - 42. "Its fragrance is positively intoxicating." (Box 10, Folder 186)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 6 1/2 x 8 1/2", unsigned. Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing, and cancelled.
  - 43. Westminster Dog Show. (Box 5, Folder 80)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 15 5/8 x 11 5/8", rough sketch, unsigned. Left half of drawing cut away.
  - 44. "We're just going to gypsy through France.", 1932 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 14 x 16 1/8". Caption written in pencil in lower left corner of drawing. Lower and right margins torn away, small piece missing from upper, left corner. A8531 written in blue crayon and date 6/25/32 in pencil on verso, portion of the A missing.
  - 45. [Four matrons in overalls seated at a table in a cottage by the shore, one serving salad to the others, butler and dachshund attending.] (Box 5, Folder 82)
    Watercolor over pencil, 17 x 13 7/8", unsigned. Rough sketch for cover.
  - 46. "You never think of them as having a home life, do you." (Box 5, Folder 83)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 8 1/2 x 15 1/8".
  - 47. "But Becky Sharp has lots of lovable qualities." (Box 15, Folder 332)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 14 x 17 3/8". Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing. AA8188 written in blue crayon on verso.
  - 48. [Matron in hat and fur coat viewing small bronze statue of a woman.] (Box 5, Folder 84)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 11 x 9 7/8". A1723 and notation—captionless 5 Ave—written in pencil in upper right corner. A1723 written in pencil on verso.
  - 49. [Matron in hat and fur coat seated on a couch in a room cluttered with furniture.] (Box 5, Folder 85)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 10 x 10 7/8", rough sketch.
  - 50. [Seated man writing.] (Box 10, Folder 187)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 4 3/8 x 5 5/8", unsigned. Notation—(goes on page called "The Ides of March."—written in pencil in lower right corner of mat. A4171 written in pencil on verso of drawing.
  - 51. [Matron, standing on large lawn, horrified by house being constructed in the distance.] (Box 5, Folder 86)
    Colored crayons over pencil, 7 x 10", unsigned. Rough sketch for cover.
  - 52. [Group of matrons conversing with the proprietor of a fish restaurant on the end of a pier.] (Box 10, Folder 188)
    Colored crayons over pencil, 8 1/8 x 6", unsigned. Rough sketch for cover.
  - 53. [Woman in formal gown, seated on chaise lounge with small dog, telephoning.] (Box 5, Folder 87)
    Pink and gray wash over pencil, 11 x 16 3 /4", rough sketch for headpiece of a page of text, unsigned. Piece 6 5/8 x 4" in right margin cut away.
  - 54. [Woman grooming cats at a cat show.] (Box 15, Folder 333)
    Watercolor over pencil, 19 x 13 1/2", unsigned. Rough sketch for cover.
  - 55. [Seated small crying boy holding stuffed dog and doll attended by salesclerks and mother.] (Box 10, Folder 189)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 7 x 8 ", rough sketch, unsigned.
  - 56. [Rear view of young woman painting, seated before exhibition case of small classical statues.] (Box 10, Folder 190)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 7 x 6".
  - 57. [H. E. H. drawing of three seated matrons conversing.] (Box 10, Folder 191)
    Black and white photograph, 10 x 8".
  - 58. [H. E. H. drawing of large woman on hill top with dog running for shelter from impending rain storm.] (Box 10, Folder 192)
  - 59. [H. E. H. drawing of two women seated conversing before a large window flanked either side by a large nude female statue.] (Box 10, Folder 193)
  - 60. [H.E.H. drawing of matron and sales clerk in hat store.] (Box 10, Folder 194)
  - 61. The Rivals. (Box 10, Folder 195)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 8 x 10", unsigned. Title written in pencil at foot of drawing.
  - 62. [Sketch of large tree.] (Box 5, Folder 88)
    Watercolor, 13 1/4 x 9 3/8", unsigned.
  - 63. "This is the last straw, Lady Windermere's husband wants her to go Bermuda!" (Box 15, Folder 334)
    Pencil, 12 1/8 x 18 3/4", rough sketch, unsigned. Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing over previously erased partially visible caption above cancelled typed caption with alternate wording, and typed on a slip attached to the drawing. Notation—(could be sitting around table)—written in pencil in left corner.
  - 64. [Matron and man seated conversing at a cocktail party.] (Box 5, Folder 89)
    Pencil, 13 3/4 x 16 3/4", rough sketch, unsigned. Erased caption partially visible written in pencil at foot of drawing.
  - 65. [Chair of ladies club addressing the members.] (Box 5, Folder 90)
    Black ink and gray wash over pencil, 13 3/4 x 17 7/8". Erased caption/s at foot of drawing. Correction onlay in upper right margin. A4185 written in blue crayon on verso.
  - 66. "I'm sorry there are so few here today to enjoy the Reptiles of North America." (Box 15, Folder 335)
    Pencil, 12 1/4 x 20 1/4", rough sketch, unsigned. Caption written in pencil at foot of drawing over previously erased caption, and typed on a slip attached to drawing.
  - 67. "The general picture is this. We went in the hole with 'Twelfth Night'…" (Box 5, Folder 91)
    Full caption: "The general picture is this. We went in the hole with 'Twelfth Night,' got some of it back with 'Private Lives.' We had to borrow from the bank after 'Peer Gynt,' and were able to pay some of it back after 'The Drunkard.' Then we did 'The Lower Depths.' Doesn't someone else want to be treasurer for awhile?" Pencil, 12 x l6 3/4", rough sketch, unsigned. Caption written in pencil over previously erased caption on mat at foot of drawing, and typed on a slip attached to drawing. Notation—could be sitting around table—written in pencil in lower left corner of drawing.
  - 68. [Three matrons with cameras encounter two Mexican men lounging in afternoon siesta.] (Box 5, Folder 92)
    Watercolor over pencil, 14 x 10", unsigned. Rough sketch for cover. See Series VI, drawing 46 for the related cartoon.
  - 69. Detached cover of the January 5, 1946, issue (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - 70. "My, aren't you glad you're not a salesman!" (Box 6, Folder 94)